Hello everyone, I am Jimmy from Marvelous Designer.
Today I will show you how to make a protective case.
It looks like this.
In this video, I will explain
how to use the hard surface model to interact with the clothing.
I will mainly introduce this part of the content.
This is a video I recorded before.
I will explain it to you one by one.
First, I will import the model model in Marvelous Designer.
Then we can adjust it in the virtual model editor.
I will adjust the model size in the virtual model editor.
I will make the model stronger and stronger.
Then I will delete the hair and shoes of the virtual model.
I will import a mask that I made in advance.
You can see that the model of this mask
has a hollow line and a protruding part.
The surface of the mask is not flat or smooth.
This will cause a problem.
When the mask is imitated on the surface of the mask,
the mask will be in contact with the mask.
There will be some unstable situations.
There are two solutions at this time.
One is to choose a mask and increase the surface diameter of the mask.
The other method is one that I recommend.
You can make a collision object for the mask.
Use a collision object to wrap the mask.
You can see that the surface of the collision object is a smooth surface.
This will make your makeup more stable around it.
We can reduce its transparency.
Then we can observe the mask inside.
When making this mask,
you need to make sure that it fits your internal model.
Then I will start to import a background image here.
Based on this background image,
I will draw a protective mask.
Here I will use a multilayer tool to draw.
Then I will measure the length of the sleeve here.
When I make clothes,
I will make sure that the length of the sleeve is not too large.
Then I will add a center point here.
I will make sure that the center point of this panel is in the right place.
After adjustment, I will align the panel.
Then arrange the panel on the virtual model.
The center point of this panel is on the virtual model.
When we are arranging,
we can notice that this panel is a little bit different from the virtual model.
When arranging the panel,
we need to pay attention not to let the panel be too different from the virtual model.
Because if there are too many differences,
there will be a large part of the panel in the future.
It is not easy to adjust it in the virtual model.
Then at this time,
you can adjust the position of the panel in the digital editor.
You can also adjust the position of this panel in the 3D window.
This will solve the problem of this difference.
Then perform the following sewing and modeling operations.
Then you can see that this clothing is now worn on the virtual model.
Here I will activate the sleeve panel.
Then arrange it in the arm position.
After sewing, I will show you.
When sewing,
I can start sewing from the center point to the two ends.
This can ensure that the two ends are almost the same length.
And when sewing the sleeve,
you need to ensure that the seam line of the sleeve is down,
hidden in an invisible position.
This is the seam line of the sleeve,
and I will make it down.
The seam line of the sleeve is also down.
Then here I will activate the panel of the hat,
arrange it in the head,
and then sew them together.
Here we can notice that the two panels on the left and right are separated.
I want to merge them,
so I will remove this seam line in the middle.
Before merging,
I need to flatten and straighten this panel.
We can choose the seam line to merge.
Now you can see that the seam line in the middle is eliminated.
It is a whole panel.
Then I will add some curves to its part.
This will make its part smoother.
Next, I will set two inner lines on its shoulder.
This inner line is mainly similar to a hemline.
You can see that after I set the inner line,
this inner line is not aligned.
In this case, I will usually cut it off.
After cutting the seam line,
adjust its seam line again.
Adjust its seam line so that they can be aligned one by one.
Then turn it over,
you can see that the panel can be aligned now.
Then here I will delete the panel in the middle.
You can see that the panel in the middle is aligned with the hemline.
Next, I will connect this hat with the bottom clothing as a whole.
Before connecting,
I will freeze the bottom clothing first,
to prevent the bottom clothing from slipping.
Then this part,
I mainly adjust its hat panel first,
so that the whole hat becomes bigger.
Then I will adjust its hat panel first,
I will adjust the curve at the back of the hat to match the curve at the back of the hat.
At this point, I will adjust the outline of the hat.
I will make the outline of the hat to match the curve of the outline of the hat.
After adjusting, I will sew them together.
As you can see, after sewing, the hat is not wrinkled.
It looks smooth.
At this point, I can make some wrinkles by making the hat bigger.
I will give the hat a woolen pattern.
When using the woolen pattern, the whole of the hat will be bigger and the whole of the hat will be a little harder.
At this point, we can notice that there is a gap between the model and the panel.
We can select the model we have inserted and reduce its surface diameter.
This will make the gap between them smaller.
I will align the front and center lines and absorb the middle line.
On this side, I will align the front and center lines.
As you can see, the curve is not smooth.
We adjust its curve at this point.
At this point, I will adjust the surface geometry and knock on the model.
And then I'm not going to merge it up in front of it to eliminate the shadow effect in the 3D window
And then here I'm going to carve out a layer of this envelope
And then increase the thickness of the rendering so that it's thicker and then you make an envelope
We're going to apply a layer mask to it
Mainly to a certain extent to ensure that it can maintain the original version of the shape is not easy to produce stretching or deformation
well
And then I'm going to deal with the sleeve part
On the sleeve side, I'm going to set up an inner line to make his sleeve
After we cut the sleeve out, I'm going to adjust the size of the sleeve so that it's a little bit smaller
And then we're going to freeze the sleeve and we're going to lengthen the sleeve sheet separately
After adding the sleeve, if you're in the model, we're going to have those folds stacked in the sleeve
And then we come to the crotch area and we can see that this is actually not a very neat line
Well, if we want it to be more level and neat, I'm going to choose a 3D drawing tool in the 3D window and I'm going to build a level line on the board
And then we can see in the 2D window
We can find the position of the drawing of this line
We can use the inner line tool in the 2D window to cut the seam line after the inner line is made
Of course, you can also choose the line you just drew in the 3D window and cut the seam line or cut the seam line directly
After we cut it, we can get a neat crotch
Here I'm going to lengthen the sleeve sheet a little bit
Here I'm going to make him a crotch
The way to make it is the same as the hand to make the hand ah, the side of the sleeve is almost the same
It's just that I'm going to give him a little bit of a downforce here to get him closer to the model's legs so that I can make him a pair of shoes
And then you can also use the cologne layer to the outside of the board and then the way to freeze it to the inside of the board
You can see that I've extended this side and I've lengthened this side of the 2D window and then in the 3D window the shape of this board has changed a little bit
Well, we're going to have to remake it and then we're going to have to make some creases
And now there's a question that there's not a lot of creases in the middle of the waist
And but there's a lot of creases in the crotch area and if I want to keep the creases in the crotch area
I just want to add some creases on the waist and I want to keep the creases on the crotch
Well, we can add an inner line to the waist
And then after cutting it down, we're going to lengthen the waist piece separately
That way we can keep the creases in the bottom of the pants better and you don't have to do the math or the simulation again
I'm going to cut it on bothered pattern
The width and chest of the normal panes are about 3 to 5 sharing
The width and the Every seas initially come up the relaxed pattern
And then I scheduled it to that point
So we're both going to go back and go around and we're going to prescribed them
Then I just moved the bands on the chest due to the position of the upper tap
It is about 6 7
I'm going to do it a few more ways
The difference comes bloom all the way it goes down
I'm going to take the extracted part
Then these two guys, I'm going to leave it as they are
So you make a change
Here
Maybe the two of them have their owners
It's like 1 or 2
Garnet
You adjust it
After you finalize it, you can put them together again
You can see that the costume will have a kind of influx of effect
Here I will reduce the pressure effect a little bit
Now the pressure will be more obvious
Then we can take off the costume during the simulation
Now we can see some of the
At this point, I will increase its gold sand and silver sand
I'll reduce the tension of the corner line
At the same time, I will increase its golden sand and silver sand
I will decrease the bend in the corner line
So that you can maintain the bigger mustachio
To remove the small mustachio
We can reduce the particle diameter to make the effect more obvious
Redo after reducing the particle diameter
Then we will get some harder movements
Add a new oxygen tube
This oxygen tube adjusts the position and size of the model
After adding the model, I will use the mode of Mock Target
Add a model without adjusting the position and size of the model
While adding the model, I select Mock Target
Then we can see that the clothing will be affected by the oxygen tube
and there are some movements
In this position, I found that the clothing seems to be cross-stitching.
When I usually solve the cross-stitch, I will first reverse-activate the outer layer,
and then first cross-stitch the layer here.
After that, I will activate the reverse-activated layer.
Then here I will adjust the shape of the hat,
so that it is more in line with the shape of the mask.
I will make a envelope for this hat.
After we sew the envelope on the hat, we can directly select this plate and add it to the side.
If you find that the top of the hat is too narrow,
and the side of the hat is not added,
we select this plate again,
and add it to the side again.
It will automatically add to the side of the envelope.
If you have any questions, you can ask me.
You can also ask me in the Q&A section later.
Here I can find that I have reduced the width of the envelope.
After we reduce the width of the envelope, it will tighten.
Tighten at this point of the face, and wrap the face.
Next is the part of making the shoes.
Before making the shoes, I need to deal with the part of the pants first.
Let it stick to the legs of the virtual model.
Here, I have reduced the thickness of the
body of the virtual model and
the shape of the model,
After that, I will adjust its curve a little bit.
At this time, I also made a long strip, arranged at the legs of the virtual model.
I will sew it on the legs of the model,
to prevent it from falling down during the modeling process.
When we sew this strip on the legs of the model,
we need to make the seam line of the back of the model thick.
There will be a live broadcast, and the live broadcast will be uploaded next week.
Then I will use the free sewing tool to sew the strip together.
We can add it to the side, and then add it to the outside.
The strip can be folded automatically.
Let the seam line of the back of the model be hidden in the position of the front of the model.
At this time, I also added a straight line.
I usually add a straight line in the center of the board,
to make a position,
so that I know where the center point of the board is.
It's convenient for me to sew.
And then it's ready.
Then I also sewed a board on the side of the shoe.
I sewed a board on the side of the shoe.
After finishing this process,
I'm going to mix up the back of the shoes first.
In this part, we can see that there are a lot of tiny wrinkles on the shoes.
It's not convenient for us to do a follow-up treatment on it.
In the early process, I want to make it more even, so it's convenient for me to adjust it.
So I'm going to apply a leather fabric to it to eliminate the tiny wrinkles.
At this point, it's convenient for me to adjust its shape so that it can match the legs of the virtual model.
Then I'm going to sculpt the bottom of the shoes.
After sculpting, I'm going to adjust its curve.
Here, I arranged it at the bottom of the virtual model's feet.
Then here we need to open the simulation attribute.
You can see that there is a paper surface in the simulation attribute.
This paper surface is actually the ground.
We can close its conflict and adjust its height.
Here I adjust its height to negative.
This is mainly because I'm going to make shoes here.
In order to avoid a conflict between the shoes and the ground, there will be some instability.
So here I need to reduce the height of the ground.
Let them have enough space to simulate.
After we simulate, we can see that this paper will fall to the bottom of the grid.
Then here we will merge the shoes and the paper of the shoes.
After merging, you can notice this.
You can notice that the feet of the virtual model and the board have some differences.
This is mainly due to the large diameter of the board.
Reduce the diameter of the board.
Then in this position, we can clearly see that the part of the fusion between these two boards is bulging.
This is actually due to the angle of the fusion line.
We can change the type of the fusion line to Turned.
After changing to Turned, we simulate again.
You can see that the bulging effect will be dealt with.
Then I will move the board to the outside.
The distance I move is the thickness of the shoe.
Then move the board to this side.
Here I measure the insertion of the base of the shoe.
Then we will put up a hidden board.
ONEY
Integrated the two sides of the shoe.
We integrate it to the side.
Then you can notice that after I sew it up, there is still some effect on this side, and we can also fix this problem by modifying its sewing line type.
Here, I mainly sewed up some internal lines. After sewing up some internal lines, there will be more effect when making double layers.
You can see that there is a slight difference between this panel and this pants.
After we select this panel, we can add it directly to the outside, and we can solve the problem.
You can also add the same pattern to the outside of the pants.
You can still notice that after I remodeled it, there is still some effect on this part.
This side is mainly caused by sewing some internal lines.
We can fix this problem by making it with a turn.
The main difference between the turn and the cast mango is that you can see this picture.
The cast mango is made up of two pieces of paper folded up and sewn together.
So when you fold it up, it will have a curve shape.
The turn is made up of two pieces of paper folded up and sewn together.
The turn is more flat.
I will apply another paint to the shoe.
considrely.
Let it produce a Irrigation
Make it richer
Make it flavoring
Then I will clone a sheet to the outside to make a double layer effect
After I clone to the outside, I will adjust the wind line of the back sheet
I will merge the two sheets in the back to become one sheet
Eliminate the effect of the wind line
I will change the wind line created by the clone sheet
I will remove the wind line and re-adjust it
I will merge the two sheets in the back to eliminate the effect of the wind line
I will increase the thickness of the sheet
I will reduce the
I will reduce the thickness of the sheet
I will increase the thickness of the sheet
You can notice that after I untangle the bottom of the shoe, the bottom of the shoe is bent.
We can show the joint point of the virtual model, and then select the joint, and then activate the symmetry.
We can adjust the skeleton of the virtual model in the mode.
And then the costume will be affected at the same time.
Then I will make the bottom of the shoe.
I made a line here first, and then cut this board.
After cutting this board, I will keep the bottom of the shoe.
To increase the thickness of the virtual model.
After increasing the thickness of the virtual model, you will find that it actually has an angle.
This is actually caused by the curvature of the edge.
And then I will make the bottom of the shoe.
After we turn off the curvature of the edge, the angle will disappear.
And then here, before we match a board.
If it has a link on the original board, you need to solve its link first.
Then you can match.
After matching, adjust its position.
Then you can match the legs of the virtual model.
Next, I will add the zipper.
You can see that I just added two internal lines here.
Then I will cut this side of the internal line.
Cut it long.
Then delete the cut board inside.
Now we have finished.
After we cut off a board, the original line of the virtual model will disappear.
So you need to knit the original line.
Then you remove the original line from the first line.
And finally, the original line to the second line.
After finishing, it will be folded in half.
Then I will use the zipper tool to create a zipper in the 3D window.
After creating the zipper, you can see that the zipper is stretched.
We can select the zipper version.
Then in the physics element, we can apply a new fabric to the zipper.
Here we can use a harder leather fabric.
In the window, you can see that the shape can be maintained to a certain extent.
Maintain its original shape.
Then what you need to know is that
If you use a zipper to sew in a closed space like this,
In fact, there will be a gap between the zipper and the panel.
Then at this time, we can combine the 2D window and the 3D window.
Use the sewing tool to sew them together.
There is no gap in this place.
Because I need to make double layers of clothing here.
So I won't give him too much of the inner fabric.
I will make his inner fabric a little bigger.
Just let him maintain a basic shape.
This can increase the operation speed of the scene to a certain extent.
Then I will cut a piece of the panel to the outside.
Give the panel of the outer layer a new fabric.
I use wool first.
Then I will increase the fine-tuning of the panel of the outer layer.
Then reduce its resistance to the fabric.
Then we are now modeling, everyone can see that there are many creases.
And there are more creases.
I want to eliminate those fine creases here.
Only maintain a larger creasing state.
At this time, I will modify its physical properties to increase the bending strength of its gold tail sand and reduce the bending strength of its corner line.
At the same time, I will increase its gold tail sand and reduce the tension of the corner line.
There will be a live broadcast.
The live broadcast will be uploaded next week, and it will maintain the shape of the big fold line.
Then I will eliminate the small fold lines to make the fold line harder.
If we simulate it now, you can see that the small fold lines have disappeared.
The small fold lines have disappeared, and only the big fold lines remain.
The small fold lines are now clear.
Here, we can notice that there is a small triangle next to the pressure.
There is a small triangle under the pressure.
The pressure value can be adjusted to the smaller number of the last two points.
Here I have reduced the pressure.
We can reduce the impact effect of the pressure by a little.
Next, I will make gloves for him.
When making gloves, I also use the background picture.
We can adjust the size of the background picture first,
so that it matches the size of the hand of the virtual model.
Then use the multidirectional tool
to draw the outline of the hand of the virtual model.
Here I will first shoot the thickness of the gloves
and the shape of the hand of the virtual model,
so that it matches the size of the virtual model.
When arranging here, we can change its shape to a plane,
so that it is convenient for us to adjust this version.
Then before the simulation, I will use the fixed needle tool to fix the gloves first.
Then add the fixed needle to the finger part of each version,
to match each finger.
After the matching is complete,
I will cut a layer of the sheet,
adjust it to the palm of the hand,
then turn it over,
so that the direction of the hair line is facing outwards.
Then re-combine the soup.
In order to make the simulation more stable,
I first freeze the hand and back of the sheet,
so that the gloves can be worn first.
After the gloves are worn,
the whole simulation is completed.
Then here we see that there are some piercings on the fingers.
I usually use the selection tool to select the piercings.
First select the part of the piercings,
and then drag it out.
That's it.
We can open the semi-transparent mode to see,
we can see that this glove actually has some piercings.
Then we can adjust its curve point to solve this problem.
If you have any questions,
you can ask me at any time.
I will go back to my
I made a layer here to make it look like the outer layer
Here I gave it a physical attribute that is similar to the clothing
Let it be a relatively hard material
After finishing the process here
I just need to push it to the other side
If you don't have the feeling, you can watch the live broadcast next week
That live broadcast will also have a version that has not been added
Next, I will make a backpack for it
When making the backpack, I will make a rectangular board
Arranged in the back of the virtual model
This board is now a complete board
I can add an inner line in the middle and cut it off
And then cut it off
We can also add a line in the middle
In addition to the directly symmetrical board
We can also set the cut-off and cut-off board
Re-set to a symmetrical board
There is a premise that
Two boards need to be completely symmetrical
Then I will add a angle to it
Set a line at the bottom
If you want to make a viennent board
Now I will add a shoulder strap
and then a shoulder strap
I will put this in the front of the virtual model
But you can see that the direction is wrong
We can rotate the sideboard in the 2D window
Then re-arrange
Then we'll get the right direction
Now the direction is correct
Then all depends on your luck
Thanks for your support sir
Then I will give it a belt version
Arrange the belt version to the waist of the new model
In addition to adjusting the direction of the version in the 2D window just now
You can also set this position in the main editor
There is a direction here
You can also adjust the direction of the version arrangement here
After adjusting, you can just align it directly
After aligning, it will be integrated with the backpack
Here I will apply a leather fabric to it
Let it dry for a while
Then make it a little bit harder
We will have strange folds
Then the shoulder strap and the backpack are merged together
And the shoulder strap and the waist belt are also mixed together
When sewing
In order to prevent this belt from being pulled up
I will first make this belt cold
Then you can see that the belt is a bit slippery now, we can increase its friction in the physical element, which can increase the friction between the plate and the plate, which is not easy to slip.
Then you can see that the belt and the backpack still have a bulge in this position, which is also due to the type of sewing line.
We will not have this effect after we change the type of sewing line.
Then I will activate it.
Activate this costume to simulate the whole.
You can see that this costume is affected by the belt, and there will be some wrinkles.
Then I will make a belt buckle for it.
I will apply a particularly hard physical element to the belt buckle.
We will increase the torsion strength, and at the same time we will increase its fascia and the tension of the front line.
In this way, we can make a particularly hard material, which is not easy to deform or stretch.
Then I will make a internal shape, turn it into a hole, and make a hollow effect.
Then I will sew the belt in this way.
Then I will sew in the belt buckle.
And then I will make a whole plastic model.
I put the oxygen bottle I made earlier here.
But everyone can see that I have adjusted the location of this oxygen bottle.
It is not fitted to the virtual model.
And then?
Then I will re-initialize the oxygen bottle in the original position
But when I do it, I will use the Morph Target to do it
Then you can see that there will be a short animation
Have a certain impact on the costume
Form some new movements
Then I will merge the back and middle of the backpack
And stop the movement
Then I will cut a piece of paper
Let it cover the oxygen bottle
To avoid other pieces of paper are affected
I will freeze it first
And if you freeze it and then reactivate it
You can optimize your scene to a certain extent
Let you process faster
Then here I will put this backpack
This piece of paper
I will put it in a different place
Let's expand it a little bit.
After I set the angle for it here,
and then merge it on the inside layer of the backpack,
it will have an automatic fold effect in the wheel.
I also modified the shape of the horizontal line here.
You can see that the position of the horizontal line now has a certain shape.
This is actually because in AMD,
our board is automatically given a smooth surface.
It will automatically give it a smooth surface and a soft surface.
Then, if you want an edge effect,
you can select this inner line and give it a fold line.
This is a fold line.
Open the fold line,
so that it will have an edge effect.
This is actually a soft edge in other software.
Then I made a lid for this backpack
so that it can be opened.
Then I made a lid for this backpack.
I adjusted the position of this board.
You can see that the hat and the board are different.
In order to avoid some unstable situations,
I will reactivate this hat first,
so that it does not produce a collision effect
Then I will give it a round shape
Adjust the position to match the oxygen bottle
The mouth of the oxygen bottle
Then we can see that the outline has a very strong outline
In fact, due to the fact that the history of the film is not enough
We can reduce the history of the film
Make it rounder
Then put the lid together with the backpack below
Then I added two internal wires on the lid
I added two internal wires on the lid
I will give it a fold angle
So that it does not bulge
Then you can see that
If you want to maintain the original shape of the circle, you can set the ratio to 100.
After setting it to 100, you can maintain the original shape of the circle to a certain extent.
The back of the circle is bulging because of the virtual model inside.
I will add a layer of the back of the circle.
I will add some shape of the circle on the back of the circle.
After I made the double layer effect, the details will be more rich.
When we copy and paste the inner line, we can take a little bit of the line.
We can take a little bit of the line.
Then, I will add the details.
I will create the pattern of the outer part of the circle here.
We can adjust the pattern of the outer part of the circle.
We can adjust the pattern of the outer part of the circle here.
I will use a woolen cotton first, and then adjust the fine-tuning of the fine-tuning of the fine-tuning.
Make it bigger and smaller, and then reduce the density.
After we simulate it, it will have some more rich effects.
It will have some kind of slimy feeling, but you can notice that there are some differences in the board in this part.
Some of them are unstable.
We need to solve this problem now.
We can see that this board has been sucked by the virtual model, the oxygen bottle.
We can select the oxygen bottle and reduce its surface density.
Then we simulate it again, and the problem can be solved.
Now I have changed the position of the virtual model.
I adjusted this position in ZB.
So after the adjustment, I didn't change the material.
We can see that there are some differences in this part.
We can simply drag it out to solve this difference.
In addition to dragging it out to solve the difference, we also use the selection grid tool.
After selecting the grid, drag out the part where the difference is.
To solve this difference.
Next, I will make a leg for it.
Before making the leg, I set a few internal lines in the knee area.
After setting the internal line,
In fact, after you add internal lines, the grid of your board will change.
Then in some cases, after you add internal lines, the simulation will be unstable.
Then in this place, we can see that the grid has changed.
The wind line will also be affected.
In order to make it more stable, I will first freeze the external board.
Then separate simulation of internal boards.
Just separate simulation.
After it is stable, then start simulation.
You can see that this part will be sucked out.
This part is also sucked out.
Use the selection grid tool.
Adjust the cross section.
Then the entire board is now stable.
Then I will make a few long strips
After making, I will merge it with the inner line just created
After merging, we can directly add the strips to the top layer
We can directly add the strips to the top layer
After mixing, we can add the strips directly to the outside
Do the double layer effect, it is actually more than the single layer effect
If you want if there is more effect
You can do double layers
Then I applied the fabric to make a pick
I will use a leather fabric for the belt.
Then let it grind separately.
Here I will reduce the risk of it.
Make it close to the pants.
As you can see, the effect is not very obvious.
It is because the belt is sewn on the pants.
After the sewing line is removed, the effect will be more obvious.
Then I will insert the breath into the scene.
The breath is now a bit different from the pants.
We need to solve this problem first.
I will use my finger to press down the surface.
You can see that the outside of the shape is also a collision.
To preserve the film, the film has to be more stable.
If there is no collision, the film will be directly in contact with the breath.
This will cause some inconsistency.
Because the surface of the model is not smooth.
And there is a bump.
Then I will use the Morph Target mode to insert the model that has not been adjusted to the size and position
Let it squeeze the clothing and create some folds
In this part, we can see that the belt is not aligned with the leg
We can adjust the inner line
After adjusting the inner line, we will rearrange the plate
Then it will be arranged in the designated position
If you use the positioning ball to adjust the position
There may be some differences with the clothing
After selecting the other side of the plate
Just add it directly to the outside
Then I will reduce the conflict thickness of the belt
Reduce the gap between the belt and the clothing
And the gap between the belt and the breathing
How to quickly locate the upper layer
How to quickly add the plate to the outer layer
After selecting the plate,
Just add the outer layer to the upper layer
Then click the button to add the outer layer
The function is ok
It will automatically add the outer layer of the sewing line
If you choose to add the side layer
It will automatically identify the side of the sewing line
If you find that it is not correctly identified
You can add it again
Add twice
After adjusting the position of the belt
I will use the fixing pin to fix it
After fixing it, don't let it slide down
Then I will hide the clothing here
And hide the virtual model
Then just change the position of the device
I pressed the point of the plastic blower
After moving it in the 3d window
I will press it again
Then I will click the button to adjust the position of the blower
In this 3D window
I will follow the blower
Click the button to adjust the 3d window
After clicking the plate
We can observe a blue dot in the 3d window
We can locate the position of the plate by clicking the button
Then I will add an inner line
I will add an inner line
I added the inner line here
Because I need to delete the internal part
And delete it
The inside part of the panel
Now we can see that some of the internal lines are a bit off, so we need to uninstall it first and adjust it separately to a single version.
After cutting the board, I will remove the hidden parts in the middle, and then merge the parts of the sewing line together to form a piece of board.
Then I will use the fixing tool to fix the board.
I will fix the board on the
sewing line.
After we choose the grid, we can add it directly to the virtual model.
It will automatically recognize the virtual model that is closest to us.
After it is fixed, I will activate the costume and then model it again.
In order to prevent this tape from moving or moving in the back, I will increase the amount of friction of this tape.
Increase the friction between the board and the board.
And then here I will add a bigger thickness to the background, so that it will look thicker.
And I will also lower more of the tail-leaning
so that it will be more tightly fixed.
We will reduce the thickness to a minimum.
Now we will add the lining to our painting.
And we can add it to the rest of the painting.
Then you can see that there are some better legs in the position of the bandage.
When you don't wear pants, think about the position of the knees and the legs.
This is related to the board shape.
If you want the knees to have legs, you can make the bandage wider or adjust its shape.
I will make a bracelet for him.
Before making the bracelet, I will reduce the thickness of the bandage between the boards to make the gap between them smaller and more suitable for virtual models.
Then I will insert the bracelet into the scene.
You can see that the bracelet is larger now.
This is because I adjusted the size and position of the bracelet before.
In order to prevent the bandage from being affected, I will select the grid of the bandage.
Use the fixing tool to fix it.
Even if there is a gap between the bracelet and the bandage, the bandage can still maintain its current shape.
The bandage is fixed, and the bandage can be fixed in the same way.
When the bandage is fixed, there is a gap between the bandage and the bandage.
I will do some cross-stitching on the wrist and wrist ring.
Usually, I will do the cross-stitching on the wrist ring,
after the virtual model is back-activated.
I will do the cross-stitching on the clothing first,
then the wrist ring.
I will reduce the thickness of the wrist ring,
and make the gap smaller.
After finishing, we will freeze the wrist ring.
We can notice that the wrist ring
is different from the sleeve.
Let's take it off and solve this problem.
The process is the same as the other side.
First, the virtual model is back-activated.
After the cross-stitching is done,
we can freeze the wrist ring.
Here, I still think that
the wrist ring is a bit stretched.
So, I want to solve this problem.
At this time, I will activate the shoe.
After activating the shoe,
we can choose the wrist ring.
After choosing the wrist ring,
we can glue the gold tail of the wrist ring,
then fix the wrist ring.
After a few more tweaks,
the zoom effect can be solved.
The function of the visual element
can be used to maintain
the original color of the version.
Now you can see that
the zoom effect can be solved.
And finally,
we can go back to the car.
For this,
I need to fix the belt buckle
I will add a loop to the belt buckle
Extend the belt buckle
Use the folding tool to fold the belt
Fold the side of the belt buckle
I will fold the side of the belt buckle
Then I will seal the belt and the belt buckle together to make the simulation more stable.
Enable the activation of the belt of the plate and the selection part with this歌
After the selection, we will remove the insert, the part accepted in the plastic pan, and the insert in the machine.
At this time, we will sew the seam allowance on the belt buckle and separate the waist belt from the belt buckle.
The belt buckle and the waist belt are separated into three parts.
This is equivalent to the waist belt being buckled on the belt buckle.
I increased the thickness of the belt buckle.
If you want the waist belt to be more round, you can remove the waist belt.
Remove the waist belt.
Let's do it again.
This is equivalent to the waist belt being more round.
After you remove the waist belt, you can change the belt buckle.
Change to your own belt buckle.
This is the part of the demonstration today.
If you have any questions, you can ask me now.
If you have any questions, please send a message.
I will return to you with a consent.
Is there anyone?
Are you listening?
This is the project file for this live broadcast.
You have no questions.
Tonight, every time we will have live broadcast.
Can you add the access cable?
Thisrender can be added.
This Falcon wire is can add.
This jungle is added.
What's the effect of that number?
Thisujein fast periphery.
What is that?
that number?
What are the values that correspond to those values?
Are you talking about the values in the physics attribute?
Are these the values in this area?
If it's the tail, then what it's saying is...
Let me create a board here.
And then you can see...
We can choose that here after we select the edit texture.
We can see that there is a line direction in this area.
Then we're here.
We can see that there's a tail three-dimensional property here.
The tail three-dimensional attribute is the stretch of the board's tail.
Then the right angle line, what it means is...
Angles between boards.
This is the sound of the first line.
Actually, the mask and the pipe can also be used in AMD, but it is not very convenient.
This costume is all designed in AMD, in addition to the mask and pipe, which are all made in other software.
Change animation?
OK
Let's go back to the bracelet part.
First, I will insert a bracelet that has been adjusted in size and position.
This bracelet is usually in the other 3D software.
Don't let it intersect with the model.
After you have inserted it, I will insert another bracelet that was originally attached to the model, so that it will have a short animation.
But when you insert it, you have to insert it with the Mock Target.
Then it will make a short animation.
Then it will have an animation effect to lock the costume.
Let's talk about how to export and import the model of the dialogue animation.
How to export and import the model of the animation?
In AMD, you can only export the costume animation that you have calculated.
You can export the animation that you have calculated.
In other words, those that have already been exported, you cannot export the production animation.
From here, you can export the animation that you have created to the modem and export the animation to the modem.
To export it, just use the modem.
In other words, the animation has been imported into the modem from the modem.
On the other hand, if you are columnist, you can export it to another modem.
In the modem, you can import and export the animation to another modem.
I'll answer you in the Q&A section.
Do you have any other questions?
It seems that everyone is quiet.
Is there anyone else?
Yes.
That bracelet
is not
just a random one.
The shape of the two bracelets must be the same.
If the shape of the bracelet is not the same,
even if there is one more point,
it will fail when you insert it.
Because it is inserted in the form of Morph Target.
If the original shape of the bracelet changes,
it will have some impact.
What do you do if it is too small?
The bracelet is too small.
So it will not be able to fit.
It's like a little thing.
The bracelet is small.
It's a little thing.
Let's talk about the handiness of the bracelet.
It's a little bit of a little thing.
All of them are OBJ models.
Normal clothes
There is no
You can change the shape of the clothes
Because of the shape of the clothes
The shape of the clothes will have a big impact on the clothes
Combine the shape with the material
To adjust the shape of the clothes
OK
Transform rate and transform strength
To change the shape of the clothes
To use the favorite machine
Then you have to relax and appreciate the clothes
The rest is not fully guessed
To avoid any later problem
We can first
The Milky Way ZB drawing process
In the future there will be a revision
Of such a period
But you can also go to the previous live broadcast
In the previous live broadcast, both A and Yang have said MD to ZB in the live broadcast.
Then here, let's adjust the deformation rate of the following board
If we increase the deformation rate, the curse of the seam part will be eliminated
If you don't want the seam part to have too much curse, you can increase the deformation rate
But if your deformation rate is 0, the deformation strength below will not work
When the deformation strength is not 0
The effect of the deformation strength below can only be activated
If you increase the deformation strength here
The curse will become bigger
The curse will not be able to be removed
And you can also increase the deformation strength here
Now, if you increase the deformation strength here
The curse will become bigger
And you can also increase the deformation strength here
Is there no more questions?
Questions in the comment section
It seems that everyone is more willing to ask questions to us in our group
You can also add us in our group, we can answer questions in the group
Let me find my project file and show it to you
Here I will...
I can't delete it
Here I will use the virtual model first
Oops, no, it's another one
I will use the virtual model first to import the large bracelet
Here, the large bracelet is the one around the virtual model
Then I will import another one here
I will import a bracelet with a size and position that has not been adjusted
When you import it, you have to click on the morph target
Let it be imported in the form of morph target
Then we can see that there is no version in the scene
I hope there is a version first
Turn it over
Let me open my project file
I will delete this bracelet first
Then I will import these clothes
Then I will first adjust the size of this bracelet
Adjust the size and position
In the form of virtual model
Increase to the scene
You can see that this bracelet is around the virtual model
Then at this time, you re-import
The bracelet that has not been adjusted
But when you import it, you have to click on the morph target
Then it will have a short animation
Now it's a bit laggy
So it will run slower
Now the clothes have more details
The grid is also relatively small
Then it will have a slow animation
This bracelet is on the virtual model
It's on the arm of the virtual model
If you want to do some
Use these models for these clothes
If there are some constraints
You can use this method
Let me import another big model
Increase to the virtual model
You can see the difference between these two bracelets
This is actually adjusted
Size and position
This is originally in the jb
A model with a well-matched position
Do you still have any questions?
Add to the group
After that, we will answer everyone in the group
Do you still have any friends who don't have a family?
Your model must be exactly the same
And you can't do it
You can't do it
You have to add a point
These things are not working
The form of making this morph target
If you know how to jb
You can use that
Use the level in jb
To make this one
A position that has been adjusted
And one that has not been adjusted
You can also use the Maya
Direct movement and shrink
These can also be
All the way up to each other
Not just for everyone
Let's go the world
It's just the same
You can assign a group
We want to provide a group
A group where many people can show up
What can you do
Right now it's a group
This is a group
In the group
First of all, you can add in a group
You can add in this group
First and foremost
I can't add any more people
I can add a second group first
Let's get to 9.55
Do you have any more questions?
I will post the video next week
I will also post the video of the unincorporated tree
Wait a few minutes
It will be over after 5 minutes
Do you still have any questions?
If you have any questions, please leave them in the comments
Thank you for watching
See you in the next video
Make sure to subscribe my YouTube channel
This is the end of the video
After the installation is completed, runners in the head
Continue to install it
Adjust andYY shape of that lans
Adjust had complement straight
Adjust length
If you want to make a model, you have to go to other software to make it, but the chain, the point, etc. are all a model.
How to add some wrinkles to the gloves?
If you want to add wrinkles to the gloves, you can make a double layer effect.
After you make a double layer effect for it, select this version and drag it to the outside.
Then adjust the speed, so that there is a difference between the inner layer and the outer layer of the version.
OK.
In this way, there will be some wrinkles on the outer layer of the version.
Do you have any other questions?
If you don't have any questions today, that's it for today.
If you have any questions later, you can add them to our group.
We can answer you in the group.